Assistant to the President, Office of the; Records ua000.005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 1951-1974; 5; 7.0 cubic ft.
  - University Senate, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - President Conference with Students Part I, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - President Conference with Students Part II, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Off-Campus housing and multiple Residence Law, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "New Patterns of Undergraduate Education", 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Budget Summary SUNYA, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Presidents Conference with Students, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Committee on the Education and Employment of Women, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - New York State Conference Secondary School Principal, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - New American Guide to College, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National Educational Association, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Student Information, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Vietnam War, Chemical-Napalm, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees-Tuition, 1956; 1963-1965; 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - SUNYA Faculty Handbooks-Drafts, 1962; 1963; 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Commencement-Dr. Steven Miller, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Community Chest Drive, 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Research Council-International Exchange of Persons (Committee), 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Research Council-International Exchange of Persons(Fullbright-Hays), 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Commencement 1967-69, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Gov. Rockefeller, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Commencement-Dr. Buell Gallagher, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Commencement-Dr. Max Lerner (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Alcohol Question, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Angell, Rita V. (Housing), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Draft Protest, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Drugs, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Flowers, Arthur(Cooperative Research Project No.5-095), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Flowers, Arthur, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fraternity- Sorority Housing (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Granito, John(Fire Administration Institute), 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Health Education & Welfare Department, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Higher Education Act, H.E.W., 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Hemenway, Curtis Dr, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Institute of Man and Science- Campaign Brochure, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Inauguration File, 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Inauguration of President of St. Bonaventure, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Institute on Man & Science, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Summer Institute 1967- Life and Consciousness (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Inaugurations, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Questionnaires, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Mediterranean Seminar Program, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Middle State- Self Evaluation Report, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - New Releases, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Presidents Conference with Students, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Presidents Conference with Students, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Protest, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Religion- Life Seminar, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - "Scope"(Civil Rights)- ("Summer Communinty Organization and Political Education"), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Shaw, Edward- Malesherbes Manuscript, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Shams,S. (The American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Shams, S. (Final Report on Administrative Internships at SUNYA), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Shams, (The Internship program), 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Shams, Shamsulabuddin (Correspondence), 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Shamsulabuddin Shams (Afghanistan), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - State College Cooperation, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - "STAMINA" Conference- Javits- Keating Proposal, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - United Nations Week, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - University Health Serivce, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - University Theatre, 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Visitors, 1957-1967 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - WHAZ Radio Station at RPI, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - WAMC Program Schedule, 1962-1967 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - WMHT(Ed. TU) Channel 17, Station, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Wuzburg Summer Program, 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Speakers and Performers, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Activities Day, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Association of American College, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1962-1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - American Universities and College- 9th Edition, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Atlantic Council USA, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Budget cut Protests, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Preparation of Campus Academic Plan and Campus Development Plans for 1968, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - SUNY- Graduate Education(David Barry), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Barry, David, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Capital Area School Development Association(CASDA), 1959-1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Capital District Committee of the Concerend- Gary Delain, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Carrino, Frank (Center for Inter-American Studies), 1962-1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Civil Serivce, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Conference on Condensation Nuclei, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Corespondence-Jan-Dec. 68, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Eastern College Athletic Conference, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Chains in Science and Humanities- Einstein + Schweitzer, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Guidelines for Einstein + Schweitzer, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Enrollment Figures, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Enrollment Figures(SCT-albany), 1938-1959 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1952-1966 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Enrollment SUNYA-Teacher Projection through 1965, 1951-1966 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - SUNYA-Enrollment Data, 1951-1960 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Excerpt from Audit Report Faculty/Student Association (FSA), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Enrollment Report-SUNYA, 1960-1966 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - SUNYA SELF-STUDY REPORT in Preparation for the Accrediting Visitation by Middle States Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1971 January (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Report to SUNYA By Commission on Higher Education of Middle States Assoc., 1971 February 21-1971 February 24 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mintes-Cabinet, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet Mtgs, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Minutes Cabinet Meetings, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet Minutes Mailings List, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hold File, 1971; 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Personnel at SUNYA (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Committee, 1970; 1971; 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Committee, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Campus Academic Plan, 1964-1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Facility Program For Married Student Housing Apts., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Future of the Public Two Year Colleges in NYS, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Middle States Association and SUNYA Reports, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)